{
  "name": "MobileAcademyCourse",
  "chapters": [
    {
      "name": "Chapter01",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter01_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch1_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter01_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch1_0_ca.wav",
            "ch1_1_ca.wav",
            "ch1_2_ca.wav",
            "ch1_3_ca.wav",
            "ch1_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch1_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch1_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch1_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch1_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch1_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch1_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch1_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch1_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter01_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch1_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question01",
              "question": "ch1_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question02",
              "question": "ch1_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question03",
              "question": "ch1_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch1_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter01_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter02",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter02_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch2_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter02_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch2_0_ca.wav",
            "ch2_1_ca.wav",
            "ch2_2_ca.wav",
            "ch2_3_ca.wav",
            "ch2_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter02_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch2_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter02_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch2_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter02_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch2_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter02_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch2_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter02_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch2_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter02_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch2_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter02_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch2_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter02_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch2_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter02_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch2_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter02_Question01",
              "question": "ch2_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch2_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch2_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter02_Question02",
              "question": "ch2_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch2_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch2_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter02_Question03",
              "question": "ch2_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch2_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch2_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch2_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter02_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch2_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch2_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter03",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter01_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch1_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter01_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch1_0_ca.wav",
            "ch1_1_ca.wav",
            "ch1_2_ca.wav",
            "ch1_3_ca.wav",
            "ch1_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch1_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch1_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch1_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch1_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch1_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch1_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch1_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch1_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter01_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch1_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question01",
              "question": "ch1_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question02",
              "question": "ch1_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question03",
              "question": "ch1_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch1_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter01_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter04",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter01_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch1_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter01_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch1_0_ca.wav",
            "ch1_1_ca.wav",
            "ch1_2_ca.wav",
            "ch1_3_ca.wav",
            "ch1_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch1_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch1_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch1_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch1_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch1_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch1_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch1_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch1_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter01_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch1_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question01",
              "question": "ch1_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question02",
              "question": "ch1_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question03",
              "question": "ch1_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch1_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter01_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter05",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter01_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch1_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter01_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch1_0_ca.wav",
            "ch1_1_ca.wav",
            "ch1_2_ca.wav",
            "ch1_3_ca.wav",
            "ch1_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch1_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch1_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch1_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch1_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch1_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch1_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch1_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch1_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter01_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch1_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question01",
              "question": "ch1_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question02",
              "question": "ch1_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question03",
              "question": "ch1_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch1_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter01_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter06",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter01_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch1_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter01_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch1_0_ca.wav",
            "ch1_1_ca.wav",
            "ch1_2_ca.wav",
            "ch1_3_ca.wav",
            "ch1_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch1_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch1_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch1_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch1_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch1_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch1_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch1_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch1_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter01_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch1_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question01",
              "question": "ch1_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question02",
              "question": "ch1_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question03",
              "question": "ch1_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch1_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter01_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter07",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter01_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch1_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter01_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch1_0_ca.wav",
            "ch1_1_ca.wav",
            "ch1_2_ca.wav",
            "ch1_3_ca.wav",
            "ch1_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch1_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch1_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch1_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch1_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch1_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch1_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch1_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch1_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter01_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch1_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question01",
              "question": "ch1_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question02",
              "question": "ch1_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question03",
              "question": "ch1_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch1_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter01_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter08",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter01_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch1_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter01_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch1_0_ca.wav",
            "ch1_1_ca.wav",
            "ch1_2_ca.wav",
            "ch1_3_ca.wav",
            "ch1_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch1_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch1_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch1_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch1_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch1_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch1_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch1_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch1_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter01_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch1_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question01",
              "question": "ch1_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question02",
              "question": "ch1_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question03",
              "question": "ch1_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch1_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter01_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter09",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter01_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch1_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter01_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch1_0_ca.wav",
            "ch1_1_ca.wav",
            "ch1_2_ca.wav",
            "ch1_3_ca.wav",
            "ch1_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch1_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch1_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch1_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch1_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch1_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch1_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch1_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch1_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter01_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch1_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question01",
              "question": "ch1_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question02",
              "question": "ch1_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question03",
              "question": "ch1_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch1_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter01_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter10",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter01_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch1_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter01_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch1_0_ca.wav",
            "ch1_1_ca.wav",
            "ch1_2_ca.wav",
            "ch1_3_ca.wav",
            "ch1_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch1_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch1_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch1_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch1_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch1_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch1_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch1_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch1_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter01_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch1_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question01",
              "question": "ch1_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question02",
              "question": "ch1_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question03",
              "question": "ch1_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch1_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter01_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    {
      "name": "Chapter11",
      "content": {
        "menu": {
          "id": "Chapter01_EndMenu",
          "file": "ch1_end_op.wav"
        },
        "score": {
          "id": "Chapter01_Score",
          "files": [
            "ch1_0_ca.wav",
            "ch1_1_ca.wav",
            "ch1_2_ca.wav",
            "ch1_3_ca.wav",
            "ch1_4_ca.wav"
          ]
        }
      },
      "lessons": [
        {
          "name": "Lesson01",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson01",
              "file": "ch1_l1.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu01",
              "file": "ch1_l1_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson02",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson02",
              "file": "ch1_l2.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu02",
              "file": "ch1_l2_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson03",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson03",
              "file": "ch1_l3.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu03",
              "file": "ch1_l3_op.wav"
            }
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "Lesson04",
          "content": {
            "lesson": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Lesson04",
              "file": "ch1_l4.wav"
            },
            "menu": {
              "id": "Chapter01_LessonEndMenu04",
              "file": "ch1_l4_op.wav"
            }
          }
        }
      ],
      "quiz": {
        "name": "Quiz",
        "content": {
          "menu": {
            "id": "Chapter01_QuizHeader",
            "file": "ch1_qp.wav"
          }
        },
        "questions": [
          {
            "name": "Question01",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question01",
              "question": "ch1_q1.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q1_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q1_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question02",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question02",
              "question": "ch1_q2.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q2_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q2_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question03",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "id": "Chapter01_Question03",
              "question": "ch1_q3.wav",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q3_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q3_wa.wav"
            }
          },
          {
            "name": "Question04",
            "correctAnswerOption": 1,
            "content": {
              "question": "ch1_q4.wav",
              "id": "Chapter01_Question04",
              "correctAnswer": "ch1_q4_ca.wav",
              "wrongAnswer": "ch1_q4_wa.wav"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  ]
}